hotels.ng 2016-12-22

# Privacy | Hotels.ng

When it comes to your privacy, nobody is more interested in having you covered than we are. We hinge our entire brand promise on making things easier and safe for our users.

We are 100% committed to ensuring that every personal information you give us in the course of a transaction is secure and safeguarded. Our Privacy Policy is a document that describes how we collect, use and process any personal information you give us. We also tell you how you can reach us if you have questions about your personal data or about our use of cookies.

Hotels.ng offers hotel booking services through its official website and other owned media (including but not limited to the Hotels.ng mobile app, its social media, emails and phone correspondences). The information describing our Privacy Policy applies to all of these platforms but does not apply to the practices of companies that Hotels.ng does not own or control, or of persons that Hotels.ng does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Hotels.ng websites link.

Hotels.ng may make occasional modifications to its Privacy Policy, so visit this page regularly to be updated. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, you should discontinue using Hotels.ng and its services. 

## Privacy

**What kind of personal information does Hotels.ng use?**

To successfully complete your  reservation, Hotels.ng asks for your name and email address. We might also request for your home address, telephone number, payment details, information about other guests travelling with you and your personal preferences for your stay. You can however use our website without submitting this information; it is only required to process your reservation.

We suggest that you create a user account to manage your reservation. It makes it simpler to save your personal settings, review previous bookings and manage your future reservations.

Note that even when you do not make a reservation, we may collect certain information, like your IP address, the type of browser you are using, information about your device’s operating system, language and geographical information.

Hotels.ng uses this technical information collected to personalize your booking experience. However, this non-personal data is not connected in any way to your personal information.

Hotels.ng also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and Hotels.ng assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

 **How secure is your information on Hotels.ng?**

Your Hotels.ng Information is protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.

Further, Hotels.ng retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.

This privacy policy covers Hotels.ng's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Hotels.ng through a website owned and operated by Hotels.ng.

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Hotels.ng does not own or control, or of persons that Hotels.ng does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Hotels.ng websites link.

##  **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Hotels.ng may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Hotels.ng to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information.

Hotels.ng may otherwise disclose your personal information when: 

\- We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose; 

\- We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;

\- We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Hotels.ng; 

\- We find that your actions on our websites violate the Hotels.ng Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**How can you control the personal data you have given to Hotels.ng?**

Even after giving us your personal information, you reserve the right to review what you have submitted to Hotels.ng. To request for an overview of your personal data, send an email to [support@hotels.ng](mailto:support@hotels.ng). Please write ‘Enquiry about Personal Information’ in your email subject line and include a copy of your national identity card, drivers’ license, international passport or  any other credible means of identifying you. We will not permit unauthorised access to individuals looking to access your personal data. 

We will update your personal information at your request if what we have on record is incorrect. You may similarly request for us to remove your personal data from our customer database by sending an email requesting it to [support@hotels.ng](mailto:support@hotels.ng) with subject line ‘Request for removal of personal information’ in your subject line. 

Note that we may need to retain certain information (eg for legal or administrative purposes, like record keeping or to detect fraudulent activities). You can also delete your account by signing in to Hotels.ng and deleting your account. 

## **Questions and Suggestions?**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at support@hotels.ng.

 _Last updated: August 2016_
